healthcastle.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

HealthCastle.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our commitment to privacy. All information gathered on this site is confidential. We do not share, rent or sell your information to third parties. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site:

####  Newsletter Registration

Our online e-newsletter asks users to give us contact information (such as name and email address). This information is used to send personalized weekly nutrition newsletters, and is never divulged to third parties. HealthCastle.com contains links to other web sites in which we have no control over their privacy practices.

####  Use of Cookies

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that some Web sites store on your computer's hard drive when you visit them. We use cookies to provide us with information relating to the sources of our site traffic. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies but allow you to modify security settings so you can approve or reject cookies on a case-by-case basis. Our site requires that cookies, JavaScript and Java Applets be enabled. If you reject cookies from our site, some parts of our site may not work properly.

Our sponsors and advertisers and their Ad Servers may use cookies when you view pages on our site. They use those cookies to collect non-personal information as a way of measuring the effectiveness of their advertising efforts and to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. We do not control these third parties' use of cookies or how they manage the non-personal information they gather through them. However, our sponsors and advertisers have agreed that they will not collect any personally identifiable information from our site visitors. If you click on an advertisement on HealthCastle.com and visit a site maintained by one of our sponsors or advertisers, please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of those sites. You should read the privacy policies of each site you visit to determine what information that site may be collecting about you.

If you would like more information about the above practice click here: <http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp>

**Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

You can find additional information in Appendix A of the [NAI Self-Regulatory principles for publishers](http://www.networkadvertising.org/pdfs/NAI_principles.pdf) (PDF). Please note that the NAI may change this sample language at any time.

Last Updated: November 10, 2010
